[As Luxor’s deep night fades away,]
[the morning arrives with birdsong]
[The paupers are
still sound asleep]
[Rustle]
Wow…
It's so hot.
[Bolts up]
Ugh…
[The paupers wake up
due to sunshine issues]
Wow!
Wow! Look at the sky! Wow!!
What the...!
[The morning sunlight peeks through the clouds]
Hey, the sky totally changed!
Wow, this is amazing.
SHINDONG, do you know
how horses cry?
Horses come here?
The horses cry…
How do horses cry?
Uh-huh… Uh-huh…
They cry like this.
Stop lying.
[Focused on being funny
first thing in the morning]
- I'm serious!
- No, you've gone too far.
I actually woke up
because of that, for real.
Hey…It's not like
horses are pop stars or anything.
YOHAN must've dreamed it.
Seriously!
[Unfair]
So, how do horses cry?
Uh-huh, uh-huh, like this!
- What is that?
- I'm serious!
[A debate about horses and pop stars starts their morning]
Come on, don't lie.
(Grumbling)
Wow, this place has all sorts of animals…
Oh, this is so refreshing!
The weather's insane! Wow!
[Not caring about the horse]
Wait, what now all of a sudden?
[Completely soaking in the morning vibes]
Whoa!
Wow, no way!
[A movie-like morning scene]
This is so nice!
Like, why were they whining
so much over something like this?
[Whiny pauper]
[So unfair]
This is so nice!
this is seriously
royal treatment.
(Yesterday)
compared to yesterday…
If we put Day 1
and Day 2 side by side,
there's like
a night and day difference
For Day 1…
Ha…
If it felt like eating dirt,
Day 2 was like
eating rice and kimchi…
[A satisfied review of the pauper accommodation: ★★★★★]
The sleeping bags were nice.
I crashed the moment I went in.
[Meanwhile, the morning arrives
on the Nile River cruise too]
[Wonder what our princes are up to?]
[Prince / Selfie / My chill morning]
Time was moving slower than I thought,
and it felt like
such a waste to sleep…
I just feel at ease.
I think I vibe well with Egypt.
[Utopia]
[Could this be heaven...?]
I came to heaven and opened the door,
[Sunshine and clouds say hello here]
and with the sunshine pouring in,
it felt like the clouds were hugging me.
[So satisfied with the prince life]
I was so happy.
The breeze was
giving me a massage.
Friend, friend!
[Time to interrupt their peaceful morning]
My friend, my bro!
[Dressed in mysterious clothes,]
[the paupers board the prince's ship]
Korea.
Assalamu alaikum!
[The paupers are BACK]
[Why did these guys show up like this?]
My friend, my friend!
[Last night]
I'm the prince!
[After the princes left…]
I must be royalty!
I can't believe this.
Our three paupers now…
Today,
for all of you,
- we prepared…
- Oh!
- A life-changing opportunity.
[Dopamine recharge]
What’s that? What could it be?
Become the merchants
of the Nile River,
[After buying items at the market,]
and go shopping with the money we give you.
[sell to the princes]
Tomorrow, if you sell what you bought to the princes
[at a high price tomorrow!]
at a high price, you'll receive a perk!
[The pauper with the
biggest profit gets a special reward]
When you visit Egypt,
[The golden rule of Egyptian shopping = Bargaining]
it's said to be a country where bargaining is part of the fun.
[Depending on how I bargain,]
Discount?
[my profit margin will change!]
Please, please!
[With 3,000 EGP each, they head to the market!]
Everyone will each get 3,000 Egyptian pounds.
[= About 90,000 won]
That’s roughly 90,000 won in Korean currency.
- Wow!
Then, let's begin!
[Self-Cams ON
in Luxor Market]
[Full of curiosity]
Alright, it's very…
But it’s not the market I imagined!
The deeper we go,
the cooler it gets.
[They must buy something here
to sell to the princes]
(At the lowest price possible)
[Spotted something]
Oh!
"There's no store
as nice and fun as this place…"
"Kind Eid and Ahmed…"
[Traces of Koreans found in Egypt]
Oho!
[Entering as if under a trance]
Oh! Mr. Ahmed!
I like Korea!
It says he's stubborn
when it comes to bargaining prices.
When I first went through the market,
I went into a store,
and a lot of
Korean people visited that store.
And what they wrote
as reviews was…
"This man is super stubborn,
so bargain until the end."
That’s exactly what it said.
[Okay! This is how you do it!]
Okay! This is it!
(Spotted something)
(This one?)
Oh, yes!
[Found some papyrus souvenirs]
Oh, good! Okay!
Nice.
[Quick purchase decision]
I think I can sell this easily.
(As cheap as possible!)
[First round of bargaining]
[Bargaining Battle, START]
[Ahmed vs SHINDONG]
(The first offer)
350 EGP each for 3 pieces,
so a total of 1,050 EGP.
[About 30,000 KRW]
Ohhhhh…
(So this is how it goes)
Nooooo…
Okay, tell me the price you want.
[Testing the waters]
Make you happy, I'm happy.
[1,050]
[300]
I’m happy!
Not happy!
Very happy!
[-70%]
I'm not happy!
Okay, last!
[300]
[500]
[Ugh...]
[Fed up]
Okay!
[This Korean is not so easy]
You said 500 EGP.
[Let’s find a way to make us both happy]
Between happy, I'm happy!
[This is our happy price]
Smile, happy!
I'm happy!
So, just smile.
I’m not happy...
[Playing the pity card]
Please...
[Me too, please]
I'm not talking anymore!
- I’m not talking anymore.
- Okay.
[Really fed up]
This is my final offer.
Okay.
[Lowered it a lot...]
Now say you like it...!
Okay, last...
No!!! No more talking!!!!!
Last!
[Unfazed]
Last, okay?
[I lost...]
Okay.
[Successfully reconciled]
Good!
I got it!
Okay!
I think it's still really expensive…
[He was a tough one]
You very hard! Very, very hard.
Thank you.
Good friend!
You happy?
[Friend, are you happy?]
You happy? I like you, Korea!
[Purchased one item for now]
Together, happy.
[WOW]
Wow!
[The sphinx spotted]
Hey, this is the sphinx!
Oh, these are all sphinxes here.
[Pharaoh spotted]
There are even pharaohs here, too.
Oh, over there…!
[Found something cute]
This is seriously adorable, like super cute!
[Found something pretty]
This one’s really pretty too, though!
[Just browsing
all day without buying…]
I mean, stuff like this
definitely seems very Egyptian.
If you wear this in a fight,
it would really hurt.
[Self-defense item found]
It has such sharp edges! Wow, this…
[Found something noisy and cool]
This makes noise and is cool
[You’re not gonna buy it...?]
I really like things like this, this kind of thing.
What should I buy?
[At least this guy knows what he should be doing]
Like…
[Merchant YOHAN’s strategy: Exclusive and high-quality]
Something that looks a bit fancy.
Oh!
[A traditional outfit spotted]
I’m really drawn to this one.
[Strategy #2]
Because, honestly,
[Offering a unique experience]
you don't really get a chance to wear something like this!
Let's keep moving for now.
I'll save this place for the time being.
I'm saving this place!
They really carve this, right?
How much is this?
[Stopped in front of
a stone engraving shop]
I wanna get something cool...
(You don’t like it?)
Something…lucky.
[Paraphrasing:
I'd like something that means good luck]
I'll carve your name
on the stone slab
and make it
so you can hang it on the wall.
Handmake?
Me, I make it by my hand!
The shop owner
at the market intersection
was carving
the stone slabs by hand.
[His kind of vibe]
And on top of that,
[He even offers a custom engraving]
he engraves whatever you want.
[Perfect for his exclusive & high-quality strategy]
I need to buy this.
This would be meaningful.
[I’ll carve it right here]
What’s your name?
Oh, what's your name!
[Gotta engrave the buyer’s name]
But I can't engrave my name on this!
[Target buyer: LEETEUK]
Let's go with LEETEUK!
Oh, LEE…LEE…
(How do I spell LEETEUK in English…)
[Help me]
[Real name PARK JUNG SOO - Decided on JS]
JS. JS.
(Working hard…)
J…
S.
[Planning on selling it to LEETEUK]
Okay, lucky!
[JS]
Thank you, thank you!
Thank you!
Bye-bye!
[While YOHAN was
making a quick purchase...]
It is pretty cool.
This place is…
Wow, seriously…
(INFP/J)
A world meant for extroverts…
[Not even buying, but his energy is getting drained]
An introvert who fell into the world of extroverts…
[Another super
extroverted vendor appears]
Oh wow, it’s... amazing...
[Listen to me]
I made it all by hand!
Handmade...!
Wow, oh my god...
[You've got an impressive skill…!]
So good hand skill.
[YOHAN approaches JISUNG]
I’ve still got some money left.
[Spotted an alcohol shop]
Should we buy some beer with this?
[Tempted]
That would be really nice.
[Egypt Trip]
It was here! Look at this!
[In Egypt, with its Islamic culture,]
This is amazing.
[alcohol can only be bought
at designated liquor stores & hotels]
Is this Egyptian beer?
[Found some Egyptian beer]
I think so. It has a pyramid on it.
But…!
[What if we sold beer to the princes...?]
Selling beer too…!
Wait, it would be cool!
[That’s a great idea]
Should we buy one and sell it?
- Yeah, I think it's a good idea!
- Say that it's Egyptian beer.
(For Sale)
Let's get one of these.
[Big bro’s treat]
What do you want to drink?
(For Home Use)
I'll pick one of these and one of those.
[They each pick a drink they want]
Hey, is it possible to get that one?
- Okay, okay.
- I'm just so curious.
[Don't sell what I bought you tomorrow]
You can’t sell this tomorrow, okay? The one I bought you.
Oh…I don't…Backstab.
[Merchant YOHAN's main sales product]
You really can't!
Promise me.
[Lastly, let's buy magnets!]
Let's buy magnets. Magnets!
[Wrapping up with
the travel shopping basics]
Thank you.
[Let's take a picture]
Thank you. Okay.
[All purchases done!]
Thank you! Thank you!
Thank you!
That’s it, that’s it!
[This was the paupers' tale from last night]
Thank you! Oh, thank you!
Wow, but...it's so much prettier
seeing it during the daytime!
I heard it sprinkled
a little last night.
LEETEUK, didn't you say that before?
It rains
when a precious guest arrives.
Oh!
[We are those precious guests…!]
Precious guests!
So, we're the precious guests!
Oh, but DAWN…
[DAWN keeps on being a precious guest]
He’s never looked tired since he got here.
Your Highnesses,
did you sleep well?
[Energy fully recharged]
I slept like a baby.
[The best part of traveling]
When you travel,
[Shopping]
you can't leave out shopping!
- Right.
[Staff] There's no other time to shop,
so we prepared this for you.
[With the goods they hunted down themselves,]
The paupers have personally sought out goods
[the real precious guests are coming]
and will be selling them to you today.
If something catches your eye,
you can buy it
- at a reasonable price out of your own pockets.
- Out of pocket!
Assalamu alaikum!
Korea!
My friend!
We're here to sell goods!
Hello, hello!
But this is great!
We don't even have to go there!
Assalamu alaikum!
[The merchants are here]
- Assalamu alaikum!
- Oh, what?
Assalamu alaikum!
[Shocking visuals]
They're basically locals now.
Assalamu alaikum!
[Led by the local resident, Mr. SHIN]
Hello, hello!
[the paupers appear in perfect attire]
My friend!
[the merchants appear in perfect attire]
Why do paupers look so good?
- One dollar, one dollar!
- You look really good in those!
[Satisfied princes]
My friend, my friend!
Hold on, hold on.
Your outfits are totally different!
Aren't those stage costumes?!
[More so today,]
Oh, what? He's Michael Jackson!
[Michael JOHNNY is shining]
Since I don't know when I'd be a prince again.
Oh, what? You look so cool!
[Both fully dressed up, but totally different groups]
LEETEUK…What's with the shoes? Oof!
How are the three of you
blending in here so perfectly already?
[Feeling the class divide]
I slept so well.
[So infuriating]
[Staff] Princes...
Yes?
[Oh, right. I'm a pauper]
Yes? Oh, no.
The people in front of you
are merchants of the Nile River.
[Merchants of the Nile]
Oh!
They came to sell you
some fine goods,
[Enjoy your shopping]
so carefully listen to their pitches,
[with the merchants of the Nile]
and buy what you want.
- Has the boat set off?
- Wow!
[The Merchants of the Nile]
[CHAPTER.4]
[The eyes cannot rise above the eyebrows]
It's kind of like…
a department store…
[Personal shoppers for the princes]
That's right, with the VIPs sitting around like this,
they explain each item, one by one.
But you seem to be
quite successful merchants.
Oh, really?
Your outfits are really pretty.
I'm even more excited
because they said the items are tailored for us.
- Yeah, that's right.
- Yes.
[So, who'll be the first merchant?]
Who’s going to sell first?
Go ahead
and introduce your item first.
[Merchant YOHAN takes the stage!]
I’ll go first then.
- Wow, you have a lot!
- Yes, yes.
Did you actually go
and buy these yourself?
- We bought all of these ourselves.
- For real.
[YOHAN] But for me…
You two might not know,
but I really bought items
that are tailored just for each of you!
- Is it a pigeon?
- Really?
But we might not buy it.
- Oh, but you'll have no choice but to buy it!
- Oh really?
Oh, I'm excited now.
[Customer]
DAWN.
[Diving right into his strategy]
Oh, it's me?
You said this outfit was pretty.
Yeah, it’s really gorgeous.
[So, I prepared it for you]
So, I…!
Oh!
[Dramatically unveiled a gold & black cloth]
Wow, it looks like a designer item!
(Swoosh)
So I prepared this for you.
[DAWN]
Wow!
[What do you think?]
I said it was really pretty!
[Galabeya]
(Egyptian traditional outfit)
[Just Egypt itself,
with golden patterns shining bright]
[and even a simple neckline]
[These two princes
don't seem that interested]
- But the color is so…!
- In gold! Gold!
[Meanwhile, Prince DAWN seems interested]
It's so fancy.
But why does it
have short sleeves?
- It's hot in Egypt, you know?
- Oh, because it's hot!
[With Merchant YOHAN's full-on sales pitch,]
You gotta wear this at least once when you’re in Egypt.
So, yes.
[will his wallet open for the very first item…?]
I prepared this one.
Ohhh...
[YOHAN’s outfit]
The absolute worst of the worst!
This... YOHAN definitely
shouldn’t go into business.
[One-line review]
That outfit is probably
[A time-capsule outfit buried in a closet]
something I'd find when I'm moving.
[YOHAN, you’re doomed]
The absolute worst of the worst!
And I…
While buying this yesterday,
I came across a heartbreaking story.
[With a heartbreaking story included]
Yes, yes.
[The second item]
Actually…
Actually...
I wanted to give this to LEETEUK…
[Ladybugs in Egypt mean]
Ladybugs in Egypt mean…
[Good Luck]
Ladybugs represent luck.
- Oh, really?
- Yes.
[Actually, dung beetles (scarabs) mean luck]
Since they represent luck,
I…
At one of the local shops,
with their own hands,
they crafted this for 3 days!
- Handmade?
- Handmade!
Handmade is great.
And I bought it
at a really high price.
I really bought it
at a high price.
- It's a handmade ladybug?
- A handmade ladybug…
- with your initials engraved too!
- Oh, for real?
[Merchant YOHAN's secret weapon]
[The only one in this world]
[A special LEETEUK edition]
Oh, for real?
- So I got it done…
- Oh, for real?
But then SHINDONG broke it!
Oh, what? What? What?
- Oh, what?
- How did that happen?
[No, like, how…??]
If you look closely…
[After ambitiously buying the stone slab]
Thank you! Bye-bye!
(Ran into SHINDONG)
But this is seriously amazing.
What is it?
This is just…
I hope LEETEUK will buy it.
- Is it clothes?
- No.
- Oh, an engraved tablet?
- Yeah, an engraved tablet.
[Happily opened up his shopping bag!]
- Oh! Oh! Oh!
- Oh!
[Crack!]
Oh! Oh! Oh!
SHINDONG!!!!!
SHINDONG…!
[Stone slab completely shattered]
[along with YOHAN's mental state]
Ugh, SHINDONG, seriously…!
No, I…
I didn't try to grab it!
Sigh…I was so sad…
[Summary]
Thud! And then…
Crack!
"AGH!!!!"
I was like, "SHINDONG!!!!"
I just screamed.
YOHAN,
you need to be on variety shows.
[According to SHINDONG]
But, everything YOHAN does is so funny.
[For that, too, is a blessing from the variety gods…]
I'm so jealous! I'm so jealous of that talent!
- Oh my god!
- Hey, what do we do about this?
- What do I do?
- What do we do about this?
[A stone slab, once broken,
can never be undone…]
(Full of resentment)
Oh, but, this…
If it didn't crack,
I think I would've bought it.
(Agrees)
It'd be so nice to display in your house.
I think it'd be so pretty.
- So…!
- So…?
[It's not a lucky dung beetle]
It's not a ladybug,
but a symbol of Egypt…!
- What is it?
- Cleopatra…!
[A substitute product]
Oh!!
[Hand-carved with care]
[Capturing the craftsman’s spirit]
[A stone slab of Cleopatra]
- This is nice!
- It's pretty!
- Yes.
Does it have my initials?
The initials…
[It's a long story…]
After seeing me break it,
the vendor got so mad!
["You...! My masterpiece...!"]
He was like that,
[You, follow me]
and then he told me to come.
And I got dragged off like this.
He's really mad right now…
I got dragged off.
- But he was very generous…
- Yeah.
[I’ll give you a new one!]
and he'll give me a replacement!
Oh!
- Like this!
- Okay, okay!
- Like this, okay?
- Okay!
Sorry, sorry.
(Grin)
[Hold it tightly]
Thank you!
Sorry!
But asking for initials too
would be a bit shameless.
(Well done, YOHAN)
That’s right, exactly.
[The second item has no initials, but a story]
So, it's symbolic! It's Cleopatra!
- Oh, this is really nice.
- So I brought this. So that's that!
[Even the princes are happy with it]
You bought everything really well.
- And this too…!
- JOHNNY style.
This one's for JOHNNY and DAWN.
[Another secret weapon
for DAWN and JOHNNY]
[Egyptian beer]
Shouldn't we try Egyptian beer at least once?
- We drank it yesterday, though?
- We drank it yesterday.
- So you did.
Then I'll drink it instead!
But was it good?
Yeah, it was good!
It was really good!
Then, you could drink it again…!
We have cold ones.
Oh, cold ones…
There’s a ton of them over there
[The freezer...? May I...?]
I’ll just pop it in the freezer for a bit.
- We've got so much in stock.
- YOHAN.
Have you ever seen ice
since coming here?
Ice...?
- Where's the ice…?
- Ice!
Where's the ice?
There's so much ice here.
- I'll stick this in ice for a little bit!
- Oh, yeah, yeah.
(Chilling)
- That's that, and…
- Actually, this was his kicker.
[His failed secret weapons]
So, you…you already drank it…
He's totally off guard right now.
I guess I have nothing
to buy from Merchant YOHAN.
- Oh, right.
- I have nothing to buy.
[There was a necklace too]
It was seriously pretty.
- A necklace?
- Yes, it was a necklace.
Oh, man.
- Where'd it go?
- My neck does feel a bit empty right now.
It disappeared…
Yeah.
[Unfortunately, that's it for Merchant YOHAN's items]
Alright then, we got it.
- You were witty about it.
- We'll come back after looking at other stuff.
[Merchant YOHAN’s Sales List]
[Galabeya (traditional Egyptian outfit): 1]
[Scarab Stone Slab: Damaged]
[Cleopatra Stone Slab: 1]
[Egyptian Beer: 1]
[Ankh Necklace: Missing]
[And…]
Just as you said, the beer was the kicker.
[Very busy behind the scenes...]
Yeah, the beer was the game changer.
[The Merchant in Blue]
It reminded me of that.
[When it comes to this man…]
In the past, SHINDONG was on a home shopping show,
[SUPER JUNIOR's SHINDONG, a home shopping superstar]
and he sold everything.
[with 2.1 billion won in sales in just 50 minutes]
It didn't sell out for no reason.
[With just one move,]
When SHINDONG wore it and posed,
[everything instantly sells out]
that size was the first to be sold out.
After seeing that, I thought,
[The epitome of "sold out"]
He's just the Sold-Out King, no matter what he does.
[And now,
the "Sold Out" legend makes his move]
Alright, my friend.
- Assalamu alaikum!
- Very nice! Assalamu alaikum!
- You really seem like the ultimate merchant.
- He seems like a local.
[The aura of a master merchant]
I've prepared items tailored for you.
[The "Sold Out" merchant in blue's first item is?]
I'll first start with something very simple.
SHINDONG looks so good
in outfits like that.
This might seem small, but this…!
It's something you can have
- Wow, this guy…!
- for an affordable price.
(Shyly clasping his two hands)
Oh, it's small, it's small.
But it looks better when it's small.
Alright, everyone.
There are many legends
about animals in Egypt.
But like YOHAN said,
the scarab has the meaning
of "guiding your path forward"...
[Ladybug]
Wasn’t it a ladybug?
It's a scarab.
- Didn't he say it was a ladybug earlier?
- I think it was a scarab.
[Scarab]
Oh, it's a dung beetle! A dung beetle!
[Dung beetle]
So, it was a dung beetle!
It’s a dung beetle, a dung beetle
[Scarab]
This little dung beetle
[Symbolizes rebirth, vitality, and fresh starts]
lights the path ahead of me!
[Known to bring luck and success]
So, this is the first gift I prepared for you all.
The incredible gift is this!
…is this!
[What’s that?]
[What is it?]
Hand-carved from wood…!
What is it?
[A scarab miniature]
The cutest little dung beetle!
Keep this at home,
and it'll guide the way to your future!
[It looks like puffed corn...?]
It looks like that, puffed corn.
- Oh!
- Yeah!
You may think that way, but…
It's a very tiny…
[Puffed rice?]
Isn’t it puffed rice?
(Ignoring)
Made with a one-to-one ratio…
- Oh, one-to-one!
- Yes, made to actual size…!
- Hand-carved from wood…
- But this is just
[Purchase Inquiry #01]
too small.
[Because it's so tiny,]
Even if I put this in my home,
[my guests won't know what it is]
I would have to explain why it's there.
[Response Submitted #01]
There's fun in looking for it!
[A product that’s fun to find]
Yeah, yes.
"Hey, there's something
in this house that I bought from Egypt!"
"Try to find it!"
- Then, they'll start searching, right?
- Yeah, yeah.
[Found it!!!]
And then… "I found it!!"
[Your Future]
"I’ll light up the path ahead of you."
[Purchase Inquiry #02]
But the thing is, if I leave this at home,
[It's so small]
my dog will think it's a puffed corn snack
[that my dog might swallow it]
and just eat it.
[Response Submitted #02]
Then, for our non-dog owner,
[Not recommended for dog owners]
JOHNNY…!
[JOHNNY, this is yours!]
Let me show it to you!
Wow, he really just
wiggled his way out of that one!
- This is the first…
- I've seen plenty.
[Quick and smooth]
We'll move to the second item! The second item is…
(Shocked by the size of the first item)
It's really so tiny.
This is just…So…
You did pay money for this, right?
[Come on, now…]
Gift?
[Yeah.]
Thank you!
[Paid money for it…]
Oh!
[Nope]
Thank you.
[A true master merchant, who paid nothing for it]
It feels like he just picked it off the street.
- No.
- No? It's handmade?
Oh, this…
It's expensive…
It looks factory-made, though?
[Lying like it’s his second nature]
I actually sat there and bargained for it.
[As the controversy rages on…]
Sorry, but I think you bought beer,
- and they gave you this as a freebie.
- No, no!
Okay, the second item!
So when you guys travel,
do you ever like…
[Q. A must-buy travel souvenir?]
"Oh, I definitely need to get this when I visit this country!"
There's that thing you have to buy
when you visit a certain country!
A keyring.
No way it's a fridge…magnet…
[Magnet]
I prepared magnets! You need this!
- You have to have this!
- Oh, you have to have it!
Whenever you travel,
you always buy a magnet.
I prepared three kinds for you!
But don't magnets usually
not stick to modern refrigerators?
- The material these days is a bit…
- The fridge is…
…The magnets stick to the sides.
You’re supposed to
stick them on the side panel...
[The sides don't show for built-in fridges]
But mine's a built-in fridge.
Oh, really?
If it's a built-in fridge, it'll stick fine on the front.
It won't stick, it won't.
Really?
And I also hate having
stuff all over.
[Well…! That’s a bummer...]
I like things neat and tidy.
- Oh, really?
- But seriously…
They're so funny.
Anyway, three kinds...
So, I brought three kinds
thinking about you three!
[A set of 3 magnets]
Oh!
This one's pretty.
[All eyes on the first magnet]
First, you all know this, right?
- Pretty!
- What is it?
Who is this guy…?
- Pharaoh...
- It's Pharaoh.
[What do you mean by "this guy"?]
It's the Pharaoh!
- You bought it without knowing!
- No!
I brought the Pharaoh
to sell to you!
[1. The Pharaoh, brought for sale]
First, number 1!
Now, number 2
[2. Manus]
Manus!
Oh, this is a must-have.
You’ve seen this a lot, right?
[This is Bastet, the guardian god]
- This is a must-have.
- This is a must-have!
You all have dogs at home, right?
[It is a cat goddess]
We do, we do!
(He's right about nothing)
Just think of it as your pet dog
and take a look at it.
[And the last one]
And the third one is this!
I'm sure
you've seen this symbol a lot.
This is pretty!
- It's kind of like Chrome Hearts.
- This one's nice, right?
It looks like a designer brand.
[3. Ankh, the Key of Life]
It could easily pass as a designer brand.
Yes, so I brought
three different types of magnets.
Three different types of magnets.
[The more they hear, the more they want the magnets]
But the third one's really pretty.
I prepared these three types.
And next!
[The second item:
Three types of magnets with a botched intro]
- But SHINDONG…
- Yes?
These items are a lot
smaller compared to your size.
There are more coming.
- Oh, really?
- Alright, everyone!
[Now]
Alright, everyone!
[Something big is coming]
Oh!
It's what we saw on the bus!
When you’re on a trip,
you’ve gotta grab
at least one of these.
I prepared three of them,
thinking of you three.
[A set of three pyramids]
[And not just any pyramids]
These aren’t your average pyramids.
There was a merchant sitting there.
He was squatting
[Carved all day long by the merchant]
and carving it all day long.
Oh, is this handmade too?
[It’s handmade, folks]
It’s handmade! Handmade!
Originally, it's silky smooth.
Silky smooth, silky smooth.
Flat, flat!
(Flat)
Laid out nice and flat…!
[This shop knows how to sell!]
Wow, this merchant's really good.
- This is fun.
- Yes, yes.
- Now, everyone…
- Is it made of wood?
No, this is
stone! Stone!
- Can I touch it?
- Stone, stone.
- Wait! Before you touch it!
- Oh, yes?
Everyone, here…
He's keeping me
on the edge of my seat!
Everyone,
there's a secret here.
[Eager]
What kind of secret?
[So eager]
He's good at this, he's good!
[Also eager]
You just can't say no to this!
I knew you'd want it, so I had
[Custom initial engraving for each person]
your initials engraved!
- Wow!
- Now!
- Here we go!
- Wow!
- I had your names engraved!
- Wow! Wow!
- This is insane! Totally insane!
- Wow!
[I love it]
Your names are engraved here!
JOHNNY!
- LEETEUK!
- And DAWN.
- DAWN.
And on the second line,
- in this country's language…
- No way!
[Even engraved the hieroglyphs]
It says J-O-H-N.
- Oh, it's Arabic?
- Seriously, wow!
[On the last line…]
And!
[Remembering Luxor...]
Bought in "Luxor 2026"!
- This is meaningful!
- This is a good one!
You’ve gotta take this with you.
[Too good for just the princes to keep]
It feels wrong that it’s only for the three of us.
[Nervous]
You've got to take this.
[It’s not over yet]
But this isn't everything!
- There's more…!
- Yes, yes.
- He sells really well.
- He's really good at this.
There's only one of these!
[This item is a one of a kind]
I’m tempted.
There's only one of these.
[A statue of Anubis]
This was a bit pricey,
so I couldn't buy many of them.
- Sorry, I’m short on cash.
- But yeah, it does look expensive.
- Is it made of stone?
- It's stone.
Feel free to touch the stone.
(Go ahead and touch as much as you want)
It's stone.
- Handmade, handmade?
- It's handmade.
- Everything here is handmade.
- Wow, so pretty!
But this is really pretty.
- So pretty.
- I picked the white one on purpose.
[Rare item: A white Anubis]
Black is usually the symbolic color of Anubis.
[The master merchant's items are soaring in popularity]
I feel like he might actually start an auction.
Yeah, this is so nice.
This one’s a bit pricey.
Sorry,
this one's kind of expensive.
Oh, but now…
There’s more...?
Everyone, just placing
things around isn't enough.
- You need something to hang on the wall!
- Oh!
So, I prepared this.
[Not a fan of this kind of thing...]
I’m not really into this kind of thing.
- LEETEUK, you don't like things hanging or sticking…
- I hate sticking things up.
(No clutter, please)
and hammering nails on the walls.
- You don't have to hammer nails in.
- I don't need to hammer anything?
[Don’t worry]
It’s lightweight, so just stick it up.
I prepared three sheets!
[3 types of papyrus artwork]
Here's the first one!
The second one!
And the third one!
But everyone,
[There are two effects here...?]
there are actually two effects.
What kind of effects?
[One item]
One piece
[Two images]
can turn into two pieces!
- Everyone…
- How? How?
It's too bright right now,
but this…glows in the dark!
This glows in the dark.
Huh??
- It glows in the dark.
- It glows in the dark?
Everyone, it glows in the dark.
- Really?
- Really!
Can I see it like this?
[One minute! One minute!]
Wait a moment, wait a moment!
[Eager]
Hold your horses!
[Super intriguing feature:]
Everyone, it glows in the dark.
[Glows in the dark]
He could sell insurance for a living.
- This is really amazing.
- Wow.
- Oh, are you seeing it for the first time too?
- Yes.
[Seems quite suspicious]
[Shining a light onto the image]
Whoa!
It seems like
he's decoding something.
[Staring hard]
Wow...
He's seriously…
sparking my curiosity…
He's like a magician!
[Oh, you merchant, you…!]
Oh! Magic! Oh, magician!
Now, look at it in the dark.
Look at it.
(Ready for the demo)
Now, look at it in the dark.
Look at it in the dark.
Can you see the glow?
I think I can see it…
Everyone, you can see it!
(Is it not…? Am I hallucinating…?)
I don't think it is glowing, but it also is…?
[Lemme borrow this outfit]
Excuse me, can I borrow this outfit for a moment?
[What are you doing]
Oh, sorry, but I can't let you do that!
[using someone else's stuff?]
This is…! Come on! This is…
[A dark curtain setup]
Now, put this over your head.
Take a look!
Go inside! Go inside!
(This is gonna be fun)
[When you block the light with darkness,]
[a whole new image is seen]
[It's glowing! Wow!]
Oh, it's there! It's there!
[You can see it!! It shows!!!!]
It’s here, it’s here!
So, two types of images!
[A set of three papyrus images]
One piece
[Glow-in-the-dark (proven)]
shows two different images! Two images!
We're selling this as a set!
[Matching item (Blackout curtain for the demo)]
You need to cover your head, so this will be a set.
[Desperate]
Two images in one! There are two images!
If you put this in your room
and turn off the lights!
When you turn off the lights,
the whole new image will glow!
[A glowing mural world will unfold before your eyes]
And that image will be of the Egyptian mural!
As if my room
just transformed into Egypt!
Exactly.
[One image that'll take you on a trip to Egypt]
The only thing that'll transform your home into Egypt!
My room’s gonna
get so mysterious!
Right?
Visible even in the dark.
[Lastly!!!!!!]
And last, but not least!
- There's more?
- It just keeps coming!
- Lastly, everyone…
[A large supply of items fit for a large company-level master merchant]
Did you have the most money to start with?
No.
- So how will you carry this when you buy it?
- What?
- You're gonna need a bag to carry it.
- Oh, a bag!
[A savvy merchant’s final move]
I've prepared three different kinds of bags.
- Oh, pretty! The bags are pretty!
- Egypt bags!
[Three types of Egypt eco bags]
They're pretty, right?
I totally need something like this.
Okay, number 1, number 2, number 3.
Everyone, you love bags.
[Perfect to take on walks with my dog, Simkoong]
I carry something like that when I go to doggy daycare!
Eco bags!
Eco bags are all the rage these days!
[Oozing with Egyptian vibes]
But since you visited Egypt,
you need to bring out
that Egyptian vibe!
- Are these eco-friendly? Eco bags?
- Yes, they're eco bags.
But with designer bag vibes!
[Dior…?]
It looks kind of like Dior, right?
[Convincing]
It's pretty, it's pretty!
It has Dior vibes.
- It's pretty.
- When you go to the grocery store, just put it on!
- Wow!
- It does have that vibe!
[The luxurious master merchant]
But this one’s not bad either.
It has that vibe, right?
JISUNG said on the side,
"Oh, that's pretty nice."
(A fan of large companies)
Wow, he's really good.
But, this is pretty nice.
I... hit a wall there.
I wanted to buy it too.
There was actually
something I wanted to buy.
[But JISUNG...]
The pyramid one!
[You’re a merchant here...]
If my name were engraved on it, I'd definitely buy it.
I would've bought it
at double the price.
(Dibs)
Oh, that's pretty nice.
I've prepared
all of these items for you.
(Eyeing the prize)
You can check them out later.
[I'll see you later when you make your purchase]
This is really nice. He did really well.
- Pretty good, right?
- I really gotta give this to him.
[With great applause, Merchant SHINDONG finishes his pitch]
There were a few things I liked.
That's right, that's right.
Everyone, you want it, right?
[Merchant SHINDONG Sales List:]
This is why he told me to go first.
[Scarab Miniature: 1]
[Magnets: 3]
[Pyramid Statues: 3]
[Anubis Statue: 1]
[Glow-in-the-Dark Papyrus Artworks: 3]
[Eco Bags: 3]
[After the master merchant swept through like a storm...]
Hey, let’s pile these here together.
- You want them, don't you?
- Let's clear this all out.
Oh, this…
[Fidgeting nervously]
I almost cleared away the beer.
[This merchant looks particularly sad]
I thought it was the one
we drank yesterday.
But SHINDONG,
you really bought good items.
You bought them well.
[Deep breaths]
Alright!
[With this order]
He must feel so much pressure.
Imagine how much
pressure he's feeling.
[I must overcome…
the hurdle of the master merchant]
Alright!
Hey, this is actually fun!
It's great being a prince!
[You gotta make it big in life]
Hey, Egypt is great!
My time as a prince yesterday
was too short!
[Former princes put on a whole show]
I don’t even remember being a prince.
I seriously don't remember at all.
[Meanwhile, prince satisfaction is at 10,000%]
I feel great because the setting is great!
Alright!
You just said "Alright" for the 6th time!
[Finally revealing Merchant JISUNG's goods]
Ladies and gentlemen… Oh, okay.
I take pride in this.
Among all these items here,
[The priciest one]
I brought the most expensive thing.
It's the most expensive?
[Coincidentally]
I looked at the princes' necks,
and for people who have the means,
your necks are bare.
Your necks seem
kind of bare today, so…
- But I'm wearing two necklaces.
- I'm wearing a ton of stuff.
[Dangling]
But, but…!
But! But…!
Those are all in neutral tones.
[The secret weapon that'll make the princes glow]
Today, I’ve got something that’ll make you all shine bright.
Colorful…
And sparkly?
- And sparkly!
- Oh!
[So excited]
Wow, but the color is beautiful.
I'll do it for you.
Your hands are shaking too much.
I'm very…nervous…
Oh, it must be that!
[Opal glowing with a mysterious blue light]
[combined with the pure simplicity of silver]
[A pyramid opal necklace]
It'd look so good
during the summer.
(Likes it already)
The color is very refreshing.
Honestly, for me,
I don't want to sell this.
Got it.
- But! But! But!
- Got it, got it. Yes, but?
- But!
- But?
[Something he'd also like to keep]
But it's because I want to take this home.
This is actually…
There are usually
multiple pendants, right?
[The one and only pyramid pendant]
But there was only one of these.
- But it does look like a designer brand.
- Yes.
[With opal]
And the stone inside is opal.
- Oh!
- Opal!
- Everything's handmade, right?
- Yes.
This one isn’t handmade.
Because this is just
[A thing from nature…???]
a thing from nature itself.
What is "a thing from nature"?
- I brought nature itself to you!
- Nature-made.
- Yes, nature made this.
Is the chain silver?
The chain’s silver too.
Just in case,
I slept wearing it to see
if I'd get a metal allergy.
(Metal allergy test complete)
But I had no reaction at all.
Oh, wait.
Then it's "used"!
[A "Marketplace" vendor sneaks into the Nile?]
Why are you selling used stuff?
- No, wait…!
- Why did you come wearing that?
It lost value! It lost value!
LEETEUK hates used stuff!
I like brand new things!
It's secondhand! Secondhand!
But!
That means it’s proven its quality!
I still don't like used stuff!
Why do you think
royal food testers existed?
They existed to check
if the food was poisoned or not!
- Then if you were selling underwear…
- So for this…!
- To check if it causes an allergic reaction or not…
- You don't know if it causes an allergic reaction!
[Is this a rap battle or what?]
I wore this underwear yesterday!
[Taster JISUNG VS Brand New LEETEUK]
It’s exactly the same as this!
[That has poison]
Maybe that's poisoned!
[This one does not]
But this has no poison, seriously.
[Raises eyebrow]
This is poisoned?
That beer might be poisoned…!
[Come on, now!]
It's not even open! What are you talking about?
[JISUNG the unstoppable seller]
This has no poison.
- He's roasting someone else's item…!
- This has no poison.
- Wow, he's really overreaching.
- I know, right?
(Stay calm, stay calm)
Please continue!
We'll give you
more time to explain.
P-please... b-buy it...
What?
Oh, you want us to buy it?
I…I'm a pauper-pauper.
[A sudden strategy shift]
A pauper-pauper. A two-times pauper.
- Oh, a pauper-pauper.
- Today, you're a bit…
Prince-prince.
Pauper-pauper.
- Oh, my maternal instincts!
- He's triggering our maternal instincts!
- For the pauper-pauper's items, from what I can tell…
- I'm torn.
I think the prince-prince needs to buy it.
And…
There's more! There's more!
- And…
- Huh? What is it?
Huh, huh?
[The item that disappeared!]
Hey, this is mine, huh?!
Hey, this is mine!
(Let me check)
This is really…
Wow…
[Embarrassed]
Oh, it's not.
What’s up with YOHAN?
- There was another one?
- There's another one.
Yeah, there was another one.
[The second necklace he bought in secret?]
He didn't even tell us about it!
Actually, this too is...
[Nature-made again]
all from nature
- Huh?
- It's natural.
[Raw stone necklace]
You can tell it's natural from the color.
- There's no pattern, and it's a bit irregular.
- Hey, this…
[That... looks familiar?]
Hey, this…Isn't it that?
It's that!
[Dung beetle, is that you…?]
Oh, yeah, it's the same thing!
Oh, uh, hmm?
- Oh... seriously...
- But what’s this, and what’s that then?
- This is…
- Is it a stone?
The origin is unknown.
[Gone]
Then I can't buy it!
- That’s how rare it is!
- I need to know to buy it.
But honestly,
JISUNG’s turban is pretty.
[Surprised]
The hat?
- Oh…This…This, you can't…
- His outfits are so pretty.
- Are you gonna buy this?
- "This, you can't…"
[Rather rigid]
Not this one.
This is sponsored,
so he can't sell it.
[The hat is not for resale]
Oh, it's sponsored.
Got it.
[That’s it for Merchant JISUNG's items!]
We checked everything. Please hand that here.
Oh, thank you.
Oh, but you did a good job.
[Merchant JISUNG's Sales List]
I know, right?
[Pyramid Opal Necklace: 1]
I worked really hard to buy everything.
[Raw Stone Necklace: 1]
Thinking of gifting them to all of you.
[The merchants of the Nile
begin selling their goods]
[Staff] Yesterday, the merchants
[The merchants bought items on the same budget]
all used the same amount
to buy all the items here.
[The merchants will make the first offers]
The merchants will name the price first.
[Likes collecting cute travel souvenirs]
For me, when I travel,
I still tend to pick up
those charming little things.
I have this rule, like,
“If it’s worth this price, I’ll buy it.”
[Not the type to haggle aggressively]
No matter where I go, it'll be around this price.
When I saw
what they bought from the market,
"Wow, it must have been
so much fun…"
I love going to markets!
Just wandering around
and exploring the market.
[Satisfied by the merchants’ taste]
But honestly, everyone did a great job finding stuff.
Except YOHAN...
The rich are more tight-fisted!
A penny saved is a penny earned!
Every penny counts!!!
Just like that,
[A wallet that's hard to even pry open]
I want to save.
[Mission: Break even!]
My goal is to at least get my money back!
Maybe bump it up to 100,000 won?
If I can up it that much.
[Reality check: At least break even]
Let’s just hit that 90,000 won mark.
[It’s all about the energy]
This is pure momentum!
This is all about the energy!
You can't give them
a chance to talk!
I’m just gonna keep
[Aiming to sell everything with sheer momentum]
saying the good things about it!
[Staff] If I can tell you
about the Egyptian pound exchange rate…
To convert to Korean won,
[Easy calculation: 1 pound = around 30 won]
you just multiply by 30
30?
[1 pound = around 30 won]
So 1,000 Egyptian pounds is about 30,000 won.
[1,000 pounds = around 30,000 won]
Oh, so 1,000 is 30,000 won.
Just how much did you get?
I think JISUNG
kind of got ripped off.
[A modest list compared to the other vendors]
I know, right?
From what I can tell,
I bet he got played by the vendors
because he seems too innocent.
Seriously, how much
did you spend to buy it…
Let's hear the prices!
[The first sale]
It was the very first item.
Merchant YOHAN.
That outfit!
[Egyptian traditional outfit]
How much is this?
It's so cool.
Oh, nice!
Oh, oh!
(Love it)
But I do kinda wanna buy it.
Oh, but I'm not shopping for me.
(You gonna buy it?)
[First, checking the price]
[0]
[650]
[650 pounds (about 19,500 won)]
He told the staff 650 pounds.
(Happiness Evangelist)
You happy, I’m happy.
[650]
[300]
[Let’s try cutting it in half first]
[Nope]
How about…
[550]
100 discount?
100 discount!
[Still too soon to compromise]
Oh, no, no! Okay.
[550]
[400]
(Reading the room)
Okay.
Happy, happy!
[400]
[500]
Wow!
[One tough Happiness Evangelist]
Between, between.
[500]
[450]
Let’s go with this, seriously!
[Deal!]
[Successfully haggled: 650 pounds / 450 pounds]
Okay, okay, okay, okay!
He really made it fun!
[Properly looking at it in detail]
Large size.
Yes, yes, yes.
Extra large.
I don't think
it's your personal color.
It's a large, though?
- A large size.
- Yeah.
I'll offer 1,200 pounds!
If it's 1,200 pounds…
[Buying price: 450 pounds]
Yes, 1,200 pounds.
[Selling price: 1,200 pounds]
36,000 won?
[Price increased to 2.7 times the original]
But 36,000 won is kinda pricey.
What?
When we go to Thailand,
we always buy stuff like this.
Oh, right!
If this were 3,000 or 5,000 won,
you'd have money left over.
[Like the Happiness Evangelist, he asks for a counteroffer]
Then please make an offer first for me.
I’m not making an offer.
No, no!
[DAWN is a smart shopper]
Good job, DAWN. You're good at this.
It's so my vibe.
[Hmm...]
I won't make any offer on this.
But, uh…
You really don't want it?
Let's hear him out for everything.
How much is this?
That’s a bit pricey.
[Cleopatra Stone Slab]
Oh yeah? How much exactly?
- I kind of want this one.
- At the market,
there were only a handful of people
who were working on this by hand.
(Handcrafted premium)
So I paid quite a bit more for this.
[Intrigued]
There’s definitely some value here.
So, how much?
Then, if I give you
a bit of a discount,
1,800 pounds.
[Selling price: 1,800 pounds]
That's around 50 to 60,000 won.
- Around 50,000 won.
- 50,000 won. Around there.
I bought it for 2,000 pounds.
[1,500]
[Around 45,000 won]
[Offered 1,500 pounds]
1,500 pounds, okay, okay.
[Emphasized 3 days of handcrafting]
Three days’ work!
Oh, you worked on it for three days.
[Handcrafted confirmed]
[Bought for 1,500 pounds]
(Really paid a lot for it)
This one was actually really expensive.
It's all good, but…
[A weight issue]
It’s way too heavy.
When you take it to Korea,
it'll make your suitcase heavier.
[A fragility issue]
And I'm afraid it'll break.
- It can break like this…
- Exactly.
I'll carry it!
- Oh, delivery service?
- A delivery service.
[Free shipping]
Delivery?
I'll carry it with me.
How much is the shipping?
[International shipping, but it’s free]
The shipping’s free.
- Oh, it can even be delivered!
- I'll carry it.
Not bad!
Wait, for just
these two items alone,
[Egyptian Traditional Outfit: 1,200 pounds]
the price is
[Cleopatra Stone Slab: 1,800 pounds]
way higher than I anticipated.
Then, from what I can tell,
- they must've gotten around 100,000 won.
- Yeah.
Then for the outfit…!
A mega sale!
- A mega sale!
- With the mega sale…
How much did I quote
earlier again?
(He's the seller)
(He's the customer)
1,200 pounds.
[Egyptian Traditional Outfit: 1,200 pounds]
I said it was 1,200 pounds, right?
Mega sale!
[Discounted price: 700 pounds]
[A flash sale]
I seriously can't go any lower.
- Seriously, 700 pounds!
- 21,000 won.
Even that’s pricey.
- Really?
- Yeah.
[Discounted price: 650 pounds]
[Expected fair price: 3,000 won - 5,000 won]
This should honestly be around 3,000 to 5,000 won.
- Isn't it a matter of whether it'll sell or not?
- 3…000 won?
I actually thought 10,000 won.
[10,000 won...!]
10,000 won?
But you're not gonna buy it.
(Shakes head)
Nope, nope.
[Firm]
It doesn't fit my personal color.
Then, that one…
[The prince’s offer]
Then, let's do it like this.
When it doesn’t sell,
pull a "The boss has gone mad" mega sale.
[Instantly on board]
The boss has gone mad!
Then, I'll…
Oh…but this cracked…
- I was hoping you'd buy it.
- Oh, really?
Why would you
want me to buy a broken item…
[Because the story behind it matters...]
It’s got an engraving and all.
Oh, because of the story behind it.
But keeping broken stuff at home
messes with your feng shui.
Oh, right, right!
[The Chicago guy knows his feng shui]
- It even has his name engraved on it.
- Yeah, yeah.
They say if your phone screen cracks,
you gotta change it ASAP!
True, having a broken mirror at home
makes your luck go away.
Yeah, it said your luck goes away.
[Egyptian Traditional Outfit]
One, two, three items!
[Cleopatra Stone Slab]
Then, for these three,
[Egyptian Beer]
2,500 pounds.
[A bundle deal for 2,500 pounds]
[Hmm...]
2,500 would be…
Around 75,000 won?
- That's quite pricey!
- Then…
Why does it feel like
it just got even more expensive??
[Giving up]
I’m done, that’s it for me!
Then…
[Discounted price: 2,000 pounds]
2,000 pounds.
2,000 pounds,
about 60,000 won.
60,000 won.
The beer must be really pricey.
[So how much is it?]
Yeah, how much is the beer?
- The beer was a bit expensive.
- Oh, really?
Because it’s hard
to find alcohol around here.
The beer's only 1,500 won each?
YOHAN's buying it for me!
[About 6,000 won]
[Bought 4 beers for 200 pounds]
[Egyptian Beer buying price: 200 pounds]
But yeah, there really aren’t many places selling alcohol.
[Justifying the high price through scarcity marketing]
There was literally only one spot that did.
Like, if there had been 3 cans of beer,
It probably would’ve
looked way more legit.
- He drank two cans himself.
- Yeah, so there's only one can left.
But!
We drank it together.
[The paupers' beer party last night]
This is SHINDONG's.
Tomorrow!
[Self-consumed while wishing to become a prince]
To become princes!
I wanna be a prince!
We got it, for now.
[YOHAN’s items are on hold]
We'll think it over.
I really gotta think this through.
[Second sale: Merchant JISUNG]
Merchant JISUNG.
[Clap!]
Ha!
- Yes!
- Two necklaces.
[Entering with a lot of hype]
Whoo!
I think he has to sell
the necklaces at a high price.
[Clap!]
That one!
That's a real gem!
But seriously,
opals are quite expensive.
Yes, they're really expensive.
[Oh, really?]
Oh, they're usually expensive?
- It's a natural stone.
- This must be around 90,000 won.
First, it doesn't have any poison.
And it's one of a kind in the world...
Seriously, this is…
This is one of a kind…
Aren't there different variations
of the same thing?
This is the only one with color!
But I realized this
after seeing it.
I don't think I'm a fan of opal.
- Oh, you don't really want it.
- Yeah.
- Everyone's got their own thing that they like.
- Yes.
[Swoosh]
But it is pretty.
It kind of has
a Tiffany & Co. vibe.
[Snap!]
That’s right, that’s right.
Huh? But…
- Oh, wait.
- Huh?
There's another one
exactly like this!
- Hey, there's a lot!
- Huh?
I... I
[More "one-of-a-kind" items than expected]
The same kind of thing…
[Urgent]
I actually uploaded that earlier!
[Shameless]
Yeah, I uploaded that earlier.
[The Gen Z merchant even sells online]
Oh, you even sell online?
How much?
Let's check the price.
(Nervous)
I'll check the price.
Wait…
You can't…use the phone.
(Can’t hear)
- Oh, because this…
- It's ch…cheating…
- The person buying has to check carefully before buying.
- That's right, that's right.
[Anxious...]
UK... No, wait.
(Looking up the Korean price)
I think this is that.
121 lira?
But I’m really curious
how much it actually costs.
[So curious]
I'm curious. I'm also very curious.
[Curious here too]
It was pretty expensive.
In Korean won.
- In Korean won?
- Yeah.
[ctrl+c]
Republic of Korea.
[ctrl+v]
He's really bad
at using the cellphone!
- Oh, here it is!
- Yeah.
Huh?
240,000 won.
- Oh, it's still quite pricey.
- Yeah.
[Nice]
It's expensive, it's expensive.
It's pricey.
Was that person an angel?
"Was that person an angel"…
[Dummy]
Don't say things like that! Don't say it!
No, so this is
- what's being sold at a store!
- Right, because it's now being distributed.
So 240,000 won?
- But I did bargain.
- How much after the discount?
[Snap]
[Opal necklace]
120,000 won.
[Selling price: Around 4,000 pounds]
- Wow, you cut it down a lot!
- You got a big discount!
It does look like DAWN's style.
- This?
- It's not? It's not?
[Quick appeal]
I think it really suits
[Sniff, sniff]
someone sexy.
It really is pretty.
Oh, but it's way too expensive.
How much were you thinking?
Me? How much?
Oh…
[Opal Necklace selling price: Around 4,000 pounds]
(120,000 won)
About…
600 pounds…?
- 600 pounds?
- 18,000 won?
[Opal necklace selling price: Around 4,000 pounds]
600 pounds.
27,000 won.
[Offer price: -85%]
Oh, 600 pounds…
[600 pounds: About 18,000 won]
That’s only 18,000 won.
I know some
professional vendors
in the Jongno area.
They give me really good deals.
Oh…
[A prince with industry connections]
It honestly doesn't give me much of an incentive.
- Since he knows the market price.
- Since he knows it!
[Unexpected insider info]
Someone you know will give you a better deal.
Just put it down...
JISUNG…
You've been rubbing
your hands a lot since yesterday.
[His hands got busy
whenever he was in trouble]
[Very transparent
about his mental state]
(Made another appearance today)
Please think over
my offer of 600 pounds.
[You want me to think about -85%?]
Uh…
I’ll… think it over, yeah.
[Third sale: Merchant SHINDONG]
Alright, everyone, let’s go.
I have to think
of myself as a tourist!
[Picking souvenirs from a tourist’s POV]
The magnets are pretty.
Oh, good!
[Winning them over with variety!]
Oh, nice!
Oh, this is pretty!
[As many as 14 items,
including freebies]
I decided to buy
several inexpensive souvenirs
that would remind them
of this place,
[Strategist SHINDONG’s choice]
so I could still make a good profit even if I didn’t sell them all.
[Diversifying investments rather than going all-in]
That was my thought process.
[Starting lightly with the magnets]
Let's first start with each of these.
I'll give it to you for cheap!
5 dollars!
[Three types of magnets]
5 dollars each!
[Selling price: 250 pounds each]
5 dollars?
(About 7,500 won)
Just an easy 5 dollars.
7,500 won.
For one?
Or for all three?
For one!
Yeah, you have to
buy them one by one.
Come on!
Just give it to me for 5,000 won.
But 5,000 won is
actually a bit pricey.
5,000 won is pricey?
Have you never
bought magnets before?
[Nope]
I haven't.
How can 5,000 won be expensive?
[First time showing interest]
I’ll take 2 for 10,000 won.
- 2 for 10,000 won?
- Yes.
(Thinking)
2 for 10,000 won?
- Okay.
- 3 for 10,000 won!
It’d be awkward
for the last one left over.
3 for 10,000 won is way too cheap.
- I’m basically selling at a loss.
- Oh, really?
[Magnet / Magnet / Magnet]
I’ll give you 3 for 13,000 won!
[Bundle selling price: Around 433 pounds]
Oh, 3,000 won? I want it nice and even.
- 2 for 10,000 won.
2 for 10,000 won,
3 for 13,000 won.
Which would you like?
He sure is good at this.
[Persistent]
3 for 11,000 won.
[Rejection]
No, but 11,000 won is too little…
- 3 for 11,000 won.
- 11,000 won is a no-go.
- 3 for 11,500 won.
- Oh, nope, no way.
- I'm not selling to this person.
- 12,000 won!
[Not selling to you]
No, I'm not selling! I'm not selling to this person!
[Upset]
You won't take 12,000 won?
I won’t, I won’t, yeah.
[Re-approaching the first bidder]
2 for 10,000 won, 3 for 13,000 won.
[No change: 2 for 10,000 won]
I’ll do 2 for 10,000 won.
2 for 10,000 won!
Which ones will you choose?
- I’ll take these 2.
- Okay!
[Sold]
Wow, you bought it right away.
- But since he picked first.
- You're already buying?
[A smooth deal! Today's first purchase]
10,000 won! 2 for 10,000 won.
Only one left!
Hey, this is pretty.
I want to buy this.
How much?
Clearance sale?
- Clearance sale…?
- Clearance sale!
How can this be a clearance sale?
[Clearance frenzy]
Clearance, clearance, clearance, clearance!
This person
just bought 2 for 10,000 won.
I can't sell it for
anything less than that!
No, since there's one left!
- A quick sale.
- No, no.
- I'm not selling.
Oh, wait, wait!
How much are you thinking then?
Because he bought
2 for 10,000 won.
You have to pay
at least 5,000 won.
No, you have to get
rid of the one left…
I'm not selling.
3,000 won!
[NO]
No way! Then…
Then, I would have
just given it to him!
No.
If you just gave it to him,
then you wouldn't get 3,000 won.
If you give it to me,
you will get 3,000 won.
Then he might not have bought it.
But he already bought it!
Did you buy it?
Is it a done deal?
Yes, I'm done.
- 3,000 won.
- Wait, hold up!
2,000 won.
It's basically a clearance sale!
[A smooth negotiator]
[Bargaining once again]
2,000 won, 2,000 won!
But, honestly…
- No, no.
- Why not?
How much is 2,000 won?
It's not even 1 dollar!
- DAWN's not even thinking about buying it.
- No.
Otherwise,
it's just gonna get thrown away!
Do you want it to be trash,
or do you want to sell it for 1,000 won?
[Knocked off another 1,000 won]
Wait, right now…
I paid 5,000 won for one of these!
Then, I'll just take it instead.
3,000 won?
Let’s settle for 1,500 won.
[What are you saying...?]
What are you even talking about?
[1,000 won / 3,000 won]
I want 1,000 won, you want 3,000 won.
[1,500 won]
So let’s meet in the middle at 1,500 won.
What's with this guy?
I'm not selling!
Oh, wait a sec!
3,000 won! 3,000 won!
You can't sell it for 2,000 won?
We're moving on
to the next item, everyone!
It glows in the dark!
[3 types of glow-in-the-dark papyrus art]
It glows in the dark, everyone!
It'd be perfect
in a home with kids!
[Papyrus Art selling price: 1,000 pounds each]
It's 30,000 won each.
(One piece /30,000 won)
[Silence...]
[Strong preferences]
Not me.
I bought three,
so each person can get one!
Oh…I'm starting to soften up…
No, no!
- I was thinking of all of you…
- I'm curious about the price of this one.
I thought about JOHNNY,
who's long and lean,
- and picked this one.
- Oh, really? What about this one?
[Smooth talker]
This is LEETEUK, the angel with wings!
- Oh, is that so?
- Yes.
- What about this one?
- And…
Anyone can tell that's DAWN!
[Finale]
"DAWN" as in "Shoot it down there!"
[Explanation sealed with confidence]
It's DAWN, DAWN!
- Wow!
- DAWN!
You nailed it.
It's definitely DAWN.
[Touched]
Wow, seriously!
Back in the day, you know
those inventors selling their gadgets
would sometimes visit schools
[Curiosity overload]
and suddenly start up the power trimmers,
[A demo that grabs your eye]
and they'd start buzzing and cutting,
and the kids would go absolutely wild?
When SHINDONG starts talking,
it takes me back to my childhood.
[A master merchant is a master merchant]
There’s a reason SHINDONG does so much business.
[Encore]
Whether the horse jumps up or comes down,
- it's still DAWN!
- He's such a businessman!
This one is DAWN's.
[Just handing it over first]
The slim and sleek one is JOHNNY's.
[The princes take it as if enchanted]
The wingless angel is LEETEUK's.
I'll offer an unprecedented price!
You can have it
for the original price.
[Papyrus Art discount price: Around 666 pounds]
Let's go with 20,000 won each. 20,000 won!
(One piece/20,000 won)
What's the original price per piece?
- 20,000 won. I paid 20,000 won for it.
- For real?
[Slowly getting captivated by his words]
Wow, you’re such a smooth talker.
[He gives no room to think and moves onto the next item]
Honestly, this is the main item!
- This is the main item.
- That's right, yes.
[3 types of pyramids]
You have to buy this one.
This is just…
[Naturally handed each of them over]
You have to take it. There's no way around it!
How much is this?
[Pyramid selling price: About 1,000 pounds]
It’s 30,000 won each, 30,000 won each!
(One piece/30,000 won)
30,000 won?
So altogether,
it's like 50,000 won?
50,000 won, that’s right.
[Bundle price: About 1,333 pounds]
If you take both items, I'll give them to you for 40,000 won!
- Wow!
- 40,000 won.
This and this for 40,000 won.
This for 40,000 won.
Why did I say "Wow"?
[Pyramid]
If I just buy this, how much would it be?
[Single item]
Then it’s 30,000 won.
[No discount on singles]
No discounts on that one.
There's no discount
if you only buy one.
If you buy 2, it's 40,000 won.
But if it's just 1, then it's 30,000 won.
If it were me, I’d buy 2.
You have to buy this one.
- He…He's good.
- I know, right?
I just can't argue with that…
And now, the last one remaining!
[Anubis statue]
Okay, this one…! It's a bit awkward to talk about.
I was originally
gonna pick the cat,
but then I heard
DAWN has a dog…!
[Tailored for DAWN’s preference]
So for our furry friends, this is a must-have.
I hustled and bargained hard,
and ended up
buying it for 1,500 pounds.
I'll cut you a deal!
[Anubis Statue selling price: Around 1,000 pounds]
I’ll let you have it for 30,000 won, too.
[The master merchant doesn't give them a chance to speak]
And then you have to take these things in a bag!
[A set of 3 Egypt eco bags]
Yes, this…! This is…!
I kind of want this one.
[Eco Bag discounted price: Around 166 pounds]
I'll give it to you just for 5,000 won.
(1 bag/5,000 won)
I'll give it to you for 5,000 won each.
- One for 5,000 won?
- Yes, 5,000 won!
[If you buy something else]
But only if you buy this!
What if I don't?
[Single item price: About 333 pounds]
If you don't buy it, then 10,000 won. I bought it for 10,000 won.
- That's so expensive!
- No.
You can't get this in Korea!
It's only in Egypt!
I should be charging
way more, to be honest...
[Pyramid / Eco bag]
For this and a bag…!
[Purchase price: About 933 pounds]
If you sell it to me for 28,000 won,
[Big spender]
I’ll buy it right now!
28,000 won means
you gotta include that one too!
[Two for 10,000 won]
Oh, this, the price we mentioned earlier.
[Already decided on buying the magnet set]
Oh, 10,000 won.
He's good at buying.
- It's 38,000 won.
- Okay, okay.
[SOLD OUT]
This is a deal! Yes, it's a deal!
[Buying right away]
I'll also buy that set.
Wow…!
Since he already offered 28,000 won,
[SOLD OUT]
28,000 won for you! Okay! 28,000 won!
JOHNNY, you don't need this one?
[A customized trade for cat-faced JOHNNY]
You can switch, if you'd like.
Then what image is left now?
[The last remaining eco bag]
I have this image left.
Nothing else?
Of course, there are!
What other things do you have?
Here you go!
[The design flipped upside down]
[The design on the other side]
No, like…
This is just a leftover, right?
[The clearance sale strategy returns]
What do you mean by "leftover"? Not yet…
- LEETEUK, what's with you?
- Clearance, clearance, clearance.
- Clearance?
- Oh, this guy…!
- He only likes clearances!
- Clearance, clearance, clearance!
This guy only likes clearances!
What are we gonna do?
When you go to the supermarket
right before closing,
the staff there says,
"Just take it."
[Pyramid]
LEETEUK, you have to take this one.
Right?
[Pyramid]
So, let me see it. The one with my name.
[Magnet]
And this too.
- This and…
- And?
[Eco bag]
And this too!
With all of those?
[Bundle price: About 666 pounds]
Uh, how about 20,000 won for everything?
What are you saying?
They bought them all for 28,000 won!
- It's a clearance sale, right?
- I'll give it to you for 30,000 won!
A mega sale!
- A mega sale is usually 50% off…
- I'll give it to you for 30,000 won.
The sale even
goes to 80% off!
[The price negotiation gets tense]
It’s a clearance sale!
[I'm not selling to you]
It's not a clearance. Then, I'm not selling.
- You're not selling?
- I'm not selling to you. No sale!
- No sale?
- No sale!
[Fine, then]
That just won't work, then!
- I couldn't buy…!
- No, like…!
- LEETEUK!
- Yes?
[Feeling hurt]
We're members of the same group…
Oh, exactly.
No. 25,000 won.
Just spend a little…
28,000 won is a bit much…
[Sealing the deal]
When we get back to Korea, a round of golf is on me.
[Secret weapon]
Oh, really?
[Intrigued]
Really.
[More than the souvenirs]
Isn't golf pricier, though?
- I'll go with that! Just buy it for 30,000 won!
- Oh really?
- You'll really cover golf?
- Please just do it once!
- I'll really pay for it. Promise!
- You'll really pay for golf?
[Promise!]
Promise! Okay!
- Okay, okay!
- Here, 30,000, 30,000!
[SOLD OUT]
30,000 won, 30,000 won! Okay! Done!
[Bundle price: Around 1,000 pounds]
30,000 won, 30,000 won! Done!
[Bonus offer: One round of golf]
30,000 won, done!
Wow, this is insane.
[Anubis Statue]
No one's interested in this?
Oh, I don't want that one.
It's too expensive.
I'll give it to you
for 10,000 won.
[30,000/10,000 won]
10,000 won, all of a sudden?
[A sudden flash deal alert]
This was originally about 50,000 won.
Hold on a sec!
- Buy it for 10,000 won.
- This is a clearance deal!
(It's practically free)
This is 10,000 won.
[SOLD OUT]
Okay. I'll buy this then.
- 10,000 won!
- I'm done, I'm done, I'm done.
Honestly, I don't
usually open my wallet that easily,
(Not really into shopping)
because I'm not really into shopping.
But SHINDONG…
[Spellbound]
He was so good at selling things.
I spent way too much.
[The price strategy of a business genius]
First, I set the price super high.
[Start high]
Truth is...
[Magnet: $1 each (50 pounds)]
Each magnet costs a dollar.
[1 magnet: 1,500 won]
But I sold two for 10,000 won!
Isn’t that insane?
[Sales genius and master merchant, SHINDONG]
This is how you do business, everyone.
[Magnet (each): Sold at 3.3 times the purchase price]
Down, down, down!
[Pyramid + Eco Bag Set: Sold at 2.2 times the purchase price]
Okay, thank you!
[Anubis Statue: Sold at 0.67 times the purchase price]
No, no!
[Glow-in-the-dark papyrus (1 type) art: sale fail]
How much? Okay, okay.
Hey, I think I can sell this
for a pretty penny.
Wow…That's amazing.
I’m good with this.
I feel like I got first place.
- YOHAN, go ahead and quickly sell your stuff.
- He's good at selling.
[The scarab slab with a serious defect]
But honestly, if it wasn't broken…!
I really would've bought it
if it weren't broken!
[Opal necklace]
DAWN was a prime candidate for this accessory,
but he knows an opal vendor.
Oh…
[Curious]
Do you have a story for us, JISUNG?
- Have a seat and tell us.
- Yeah.
[A sale needs a good story]
Oh…
It was honestly
my type of necklace…
[Upset]
But it was being totally ignored...
It made me
want to sell it even more!
So, I went all out
trying to hype it up.
[Adding a dash of pity]
I even tried to get some sympathy points.
It all started yesterday…
- It all started…
- Yesterday,
it was actually
my first time haggling…
Oh, so you'd never haggled before.
It was my first time visiting
a market where bargaining is common.
There was this
really friendly brother over there…!
Oh, a brother!
My friend!
Hey yo!
Oh my god.
[Cheerfully greeting in Korean]
Hello!
- Hello. That's right, hello.
- Hello.
- He called me over, so I walked in, hypnotized.
- I already feel bad for him…
[JOHNNY] He went
because he was called…
He went in
immediately with the "Start" cue!
It totally caught me off guard.
- Straight into the first shop.
- That's right.
But, when I went there…
[He meets the fateful opal necklace]
It’s a Pyramid!
Perfect.
[OMG!]
Oh my god!
Perfect!
- Opal!
- I like!
It’s 92.5% pure silver.
[Carefully]
How much is it?
[Don’t worry about money]
Don't worry.
Try it on first.
I’ll tell you the price later.
A-HA!
- WOW!
- Wow!!
(WoW)
Wow!
When I said I wanted to buy it,
[Initial offer: 80]
he started it at 80.
[Pounds?]
80 pounds?
[Won?]
800,000 won?
- He just showed me 80 on the calculator.
- 80?
Uh, 80?
[Total budget 3,000 pounds]
I actually have several 200-pound notes,
[An affordable and pretty item]
and 80 pounds seemed so cheap.
[Already 100% satisfied]
So I thought I must buy it! This is it!
But it turns out
he meant USD…
Dollars!
Oh, dollars!
[Budget exceeded]
Oh, it was in dollars!
[80 dollars: about 120,000 won]
80 dollars?
[No way]
I said that was nonsense.
[Urgently tried the small talk method]
So I was like, "I love Salah."
[Sneaky charm move]
I really like Mohamed Salah
[OMG!]
Oh my god!
I love Korea!
[Please give me a discount]
I love Egypt too!
I was like,
"Egypt, number one!"
[Negotiated from 80 to 65 dollars]
And I bargained it down to 65 dollars.
[65 dollars = About 3,350 pounds]
And it was still 3,350 pounds.
[Budget exceeded]
Am I short on cash…?
[Revealing his entire budget]
I said, "I only have 3,000 pounds. Is that okay?"
And he was super chill about it.
[It’s okay]
"Yeah! It’s okay!"
[Revealed his entire budget of 3,000 pounds]
3,000! Oh my god. I'm sorry.
So, we each had 3,000 pounds.
[3,000 pounds]
You put it all in at once!
[What about the other necklace?]
Then, what's that?
[Natural stone necklace]
Out of nowhere, that man
suddenly brought it out.
He said he'll throw it in too.
This is a present!
[OMG!]
Oh my god!
No money!
Because you’re a good guy.
Wow!
It wasn't a freebie.
He gave you another item,
but still made a good profit.
That’s right, that’s right.
[He sent a finger heart every time]
Every time I walked by,
he kept sending me a finger heart.
Thanks, JISUNG!
He kept saying,
"Hey! My friend! My friend!"
DAWN really needs
to buy this one from him.
No, I honestly
would've bought it
if I didn't already know an opal dealer.
[Empty]
But LEETEUK's the only one with nothing on his neck.
I don't have anything.
LEETEUK,
it is your personal color.
It's so pretty…
[Prince LEETEUK needs a story]
But honestly, this necklace…
I would have to explain it!
Oh, just say that
[Gift from NCT DREAM’s Jisung]
JISUNG from NCT
[Flex]
gave this to me as a gift.
[A good story]
Okay, JISUNG. I'll buy this for 50,000 won.
[Touched]
Wow!
LEETEUK, you cut the price down
so much on my stuff…
Wait, how much
did I buy that for again?
[Rub, rub]
[Backtracking?]
But, are you gonna change your mind after saying that?
Give him 50,000 won.
I'll pay 50,000 bucks for him.
[Clap]
- 50,000 won?
- Thank you.
Will you sell it?
- I will definitely sell it.
- Okay.
[Finally sold]
He still sold it for way less than what he paid.
[The bonus necklace]
You should take this on the house too, LEETEUK.
You can just take this!
[Knows what he likes]
Oh, I'm good.
I’ll buy this for 5,000 won.
[Noblesse oblige]
Just buy it for him for 10,000 won, and call it a day!
[SOLD OUT]
Okay, I'll buy it for 10,000 won.
- Oh, not bad!
- Thank you!
Since JISUNG worked very hard.
I really wanted to buy it from him…
[If it weren’t for the opal shop owner in the Jongno area,]
If it weren’t for the opal shop owner I know,
[he would've bought it earlier]
I would’ve already bought it.
[SHINDONG] Then,
this means YOHAN is last.
Let’s hear YOHAN's side too.
[Story lover]
I'm sure he has a story behind it!
- Unfortunately…
- Yes.
- I have no story…
- None.
The slab breaking
was the end of it?
Yeah, the slab breaking
was the end of it.
[The only story was already used up]
That was the only story I had.
[Traditional outfit]
Then, why'd you buy this?
I bought it because it seemed like
something we'd wear since we're in Egypt.
- Honestly…!
- Yes.
[Revealing the actual price]
I bought it for 450 pounds.
[Egyptian traditional outfit
buying price: 450 pounds]
[Selling at a loss]
How does 400 pounds sound??
You suddenly
became very shameless.
[Enlightened]
Oh, I have nothing left now.
But unfortunately…
- If it were something like this…
- The material!
[Totally would've bought it on the spot]
I would've bought it.
- Seriously, that…!
- Me too.
If it had long sleeves…!
Me too, me too, me too!
[The merchants would've bought it if it were their style]
And if the color was like this…
Preferably!
[YOHAN’s outfit pattern requires courage to wear]
To wear it…
- The pattern requires a lot of courage.
- Right, it's too flashy.
Are you gonna buy it?
[A deep look]
Ugh......
But even if you sell it at 1,500 pounds,
aren't you still in last place?
- Right.
- Yeah!
- Then I won't buy it…
- You don't have to buy it. It's already…
It's already over for me…
- I don't think you need to buy it.
- What a shame.
- Princes, are you done shopping?
- Yes.
[Prince’s shopping spree is over]
Alright.
But is there a prize
for first place?
[Revealing today's sales for the Merchants of the Nile]
It's time to announce today's sales.
No doubt, today’s sales king…!
The home shopping
"Sold Out" legend!
It's Merchant SHINDONG!
Yeah!
[SHINDONG: 3,532 pounds]
[JISUNG: 1,999 pounds]
[YOHAN: 0 pounds]
Wow, he really sold a lot!
The difference was truly massive.
[Everyone agrees on the 1st place winner]
We got completely swept away.
It just makes no sense.
Wow…For me…
He sold better
than any market vendor!
Seriously...!
SHINDONG is…!
No matter the country,
no matter the hustle,
[Someone who would've succeeded!]
he totally would've succeeded.
Through his excellent business tactics,
SHINDONG built a fortune,
- and he will be dining with the princes..
- Oh!
- for the cruise breakfast.
- Wow!
Wow!
- Amazing!
- Wow, that's awesome!
Are we eating bread again?
[The loser merchants will eat their bread outdoors]
Yeah, the rest of you can step outside and eat your bread.
- JISUNG…
- For real...?
Yesterday, the two of us
- ate bread for all three meals…
- From what I can tell,
[Getting closer to bread than ever...]
JISUNG just might vanish in two days.
- Great work, everyone!
- Oh!
[Following the intense
merchants' mission]
[From traditional Egyptian dishes]
[to a menu full of variety]
[A feast prepared
especially for the princes]
[Sales king SHINDONG arrives]
Wow!
They set it up like this here?
[Enjoying the prince life]
Wearing this and sitting here,
I really feel like a prince!
Welcome!
[Entering calmly]
Wow, this place is amazing.
Did you eat
like this yesterday too?
Yes, SHINDONG.
Wow…
This is awesome.
This seems to come
very naturally for you.
[Perfectly adjusted after being a prince twice in a row]
I mean, I'm so used to it now.
Oh!
I need to be a prince today.
There's no way around it.
(Prince JOHNNY makes his grand entrance)
You have to be a prince. It's time to return.
Your outfit suits
this place so well.
But since you stand out more,
it seems like you're hosting this.
Right?
Don't I seem like the prince?
You seem the most kingly of us all.
[Stuttering]
Welcome aboard my yacht…
Uh, my… What is this?
- Boarding my ship…
- The cruise!
[Copy-paste]
Welcome aboard my cruise ship, everyone.
It suits you well.
[The merchant’s breakfast meeting]
Everyone. Good morning! Breakfast!
- Good morning.
- Please enjoy this breakfast.
Bon appétit.
Thank you for this food!
[Healthy soul food Ta’ameya makes a comeback]
LEETEUK, this is what we ate on the first day.
The beans we ate
on the first day.
- Oh, it's made from that?
- It's really good, so good.
Oh!
[Explosive interest]
Oh, it’s delicious?
- SHINDONG, can I also have one…
- It's really delicious.
Try it, it's really good.
Mmm!
WOW!
It's good, right?
I told you it was good.
[Even LEETEUK seems to like it]
It's not really "healthy",
but it's delicious.
Mmm!
So good!
It's so yummy, right?
Excuse me!
Coke, please
(Glances)
Would you give me an Americano?
[Ordering drinks like a pro]
Americano. Iced Americano.
Wow, if you order it,
they just give it to you?
[Feels like visiting a rich friend’s house]
This is amazing.
[We kinda…really seem like princes]
I've already gotten so used to it, LEETEUK.
We've gotten close!
[The princes have a happy time]
[And one sales king]
SHINDONG did so well.
- We just couldn't win against him.
- Honestly, I was just…
[The paupers trudge along]
As soon as SHINDONG started talking, I saw bread.
I know, right?
(Go away)
Ugh, seriously, this…
Today… Ugh…
But this just looks so pathetic.
[Let’s stop meeting]
I don't want to see this black plastic bag anymore.
Yeah, the black plastic bag.
What? Is this water?
I thought it was kimbap.
- Wow.
- Just by the shape.
[Optimistic Pauper #1]
At least it’s a bit softer.
[Optimistic Pauper #2]
The one we had yesterday was a bit hard.
Water.
[Right in front of the princes' dining area]
They set the table right here.
My insides right now are really…
Sigh...
(From YOHAN’s POV)
[Tsk...]
[Feeling blue]
YOHAN, enjoy your meal...
[Trying to stay strong]
Enjoy your meal.
[Taking a chomp at the same time]
But, you know,
the more I eat this,
the more I get this flavor!
It's kind of like,
Pyeongyang Naengmyeon style!
- It's mild, but you keep going back for more.
- It's mild, but nice.
[While the paupers
are enjoying their own feast...]
Mmm!
Mmm!!
So good!
[The princes are
still living the peaceful life]
[No emotions]
I feel so bad for JISUNG, what do I do?
You should've switched with him.
But the rules say
we can't switch.
I can't just fix him a plate, right?
[What can we do…]
Oh.
[Slurp, slurp, slurp]
Maybe because I’m coming
from a pauper life, but I can't seem to eat well.
- Right?
- Yeah.
[When he does eat well,
just how much does he eat…?]
[Anyway, everyone's worried about the double pauper]
I can't really enjoy this. Our JISUNG, what do we do about him?
[Are you really worried though…?]
I just felt so bad for JISUNG.
But yesterday,
JISUNG was roasting you.
Oh, really?
You definitely told him…
When we were playing games,
LEETEUK whispered in my ear.
"JISUNG, you should be
the prince today."
[But only he became the prince]
But he actually worked really hard…
Hahahaha!
That just popped into my mind,
and it was so funny.
What a bad person!
[A bad person…]
Are we playing
the next game right away?
[Craving for a status upgrade]
I want to play games.
[Let's cheer up again]
Let's become more determined through this.
[Okay]
(Cheers)
[Bottom's up]
Huh?
We don't vibe well…
Is this not it…?
[Even paupers can clink glasses]
Cheers! I said, "Cheers!"
Hahaha!
I did it like this…!
I didn't…
I didn't finish it yet.
[Wishing to escape the pauper life]
Adios!
[He’s a pauper too]
I really hope JISUNG becomes a prince.
[Choking up]
I don’t know.
(Pauper JISUNG)
I thought,
"No matter what,
I will become the prince."
[I have to be the prince…]
First, I have to become a prince.
["ALL or NOTHING"
Day 2 status resets]
Wow, that’s cool.
So cool!
This is really cool!
It's really huge!
- Wow, look over there! So cool!
- Wow!
This can’t be real.
[Totally overwhelmed]
I wondered what they did here.
[Luxor Temple]
[Where Pharaoh’s time stands still]
[A sanctuary infused with the power
of Pharaohs and the breath of gods]
[With ancient records carved
deep into stone walls]
[a sacred space shaped
by colossal stone pillars]
[and endless rows of
countless sphinxes]
[Luxor Temple]
[Built by Amenhotep III
and expanded by Ramses II]
[An icon of ancient Egyptian
civilization that’s endured 3,400 years]
[Staff] The very spot
you’re standing on now
is an ancient temple
on the east side of the Nile River.
This is the Luxor Temple.
- Wow!
- Luxor!
Oh, so it's Luxor Temple!
If you look in the back,
you can see the tall pillar on the left,
- Yes.
- That's called an obelisk.
- An obelisk.
[Obelisk, a symbol
glorifying the power of the sun god]
[But where’s the pillar on the right?]
[Staff] Do you know
where the right pillar is?
Was it in France?
[So close to the answer]
Oh, should we narrow it down a bit more?
- Paris?
- Paris.
[Almost there...!]
Okay, just a little more.
The Louvre?
[Staff] The obelisk is
at the Place de la Concorde in Paris.
Oh, yes, that's right
[The Obelisk
at the Place de la Concorde]
[Muhammad Ali,
the then-Governor of Egypt,]
[gifted it to France
to strengthen their friendship]
Wow, that's so cool.
[Staff] As you probably saw earlier,
this place actually
closes at 8 PM.
Oh!
So we rented it
after closing time?
Yes, just for you guys,
(Thank you!)
they rented it out for us.
- That's amazing! Wow!
- Wow!
[Staff] Before we dive
into the real mission,
we'll give you 20 minutes
to freely explore
on your own and come back.
…to freely explore
- Oh…
- Oh, this is…
[Why the sightseeing?]
Oh, this is iffy. It's very iffy.
[Overly suspicious humans]
Is this another memory test?
[Strategist SHINDONG activates]
I'd better snap some pics then.
[It's seriously
for them to sightsee…]
[Already memorizing the whole temple]
There's a ton of bird images.
[First, take the shots]
[And then…]
[Someone misunderstood it as first-come, first-served]
Oh, you're taking the hard path.
No…!
[Pauper JISUNG heads out too]
[Everyone takes off quickly]
There’s no time to waste!
Once you start doubting everything,
you start doing worse.
[Except one person]
You just gotta enjoy it!
These guys are way
too greedy, seriously.
[Just a lazy person]
(Passing by)
Wow, they're real stones!
[Busy, so busy]
This is no joke.
You have to take it easy.
You can't think something's gonna happen.
[Thoroughly counting the pillars]
[Chronically suspicious]
I can’t trust the production team at all,
so I was trying to memorize
the number of pillars the temple had.
[Starting to doubt everything]
I feel like it'll be a question.
I took pictures
and counted every pillar.
[The scariest person...]
I looked at everything in detail.
Just relax and enjoy it!
- You seem to be trying harder than anyone else.
- No, no.
I mean, well…
I'm just here to have fun.
[Found a guide map]
Wow!
Can I not use flash?
[Sensing something and approaching]
Oh, yeah, this is important.
This is important?
Doesn't it look like
it'd be important?
[Suddenly, everyone gathers around the map]
Yeah.
(What are they looking at...?)
Everyone left this behind…
YOHAN, you're blocking it!
(Curious)
What is this?
I also took pictures,
just in case.
You never know,
so better safe than sorry.
(Checked what it was)
Oh, JOHNNY blocked it…
[After pretending not to care,]
Oh, wait. It shook! Oh, okay.
[he snaps a shot while spewing nonsense]
Hey, but if you take a picture, do you get anything from it?
So, like…!
For me, it's just…No.
But LEETEUK, you said we should enjoy it,
but you're taking pictures.
[What are you talking about? I am enjoying it]
Hey, I’m having fun in my own way right now.
They must be a married couple.
[Wedding MC expert]
You two are a perfect match!
LEETEUK's filming
a variety show again.
Oh, right! I'm filming too.
This all feels kinda unreal.
[Spotting something?]
Whoa, what’s that over there?
Wow!
Wow! Wow!!
This place is seriously cool!
This place is amazing.
[A vast plaza surrounded
by dozens of towering pillars]
Wow, there are
so many pillars here.
[A sight too amazing for just your eyes]
Wow, this is incredible.
Wow!
They must have held
festivals of some sort here, right?
This place is seriously stunning.
Wow!
Oh, oh!
Like, there aren't a lot of people
who can see this place
empty, like us, right?
That's right.
[A sense of freedom
in the vast, open space]
[JOHNNY] For this trip,
it was one of
the most memorable moments.
When we went from Cairo to Luxor,
[The Luxor Temple he saw in the car]
I saw the Luxor Temple, because it was massive!
I said I really wanted
to visit that place later.
[He finally sees it in person]
I went, and it was that place!
I was so, so excited.
[Moving deeper into the temple]
Wow, look at the murals on the walls.
There are so many murals!
Every single wall
is covered in drawings!
[Ancient records fill every surface]
There isn’t
a single blank spot anywhere.
[A heritage thousands of years old]
They're all covered in drawings.
[and the moment you face it
thousands of years later]
These are
the actual murals, right?
If you look closely,
they're all different drawings.
Oh, really?
The types of food are different.
This one’s veggies.
[The lives and thoughts passed down to us]
This is something else.
[from ancient humanity]
Every dish is unique
[SHINDONG] It's not about
it being good or bad.
It just didn't feel real.
[As you walk, enchanted by the grandeur,
a path that appears like a miracle]
- Leaving behind the grand sightseeing.
- Yes.
[Staff] It’s time to
decide your status with a game.
Please!
There was a reason
they told us to wear sneakers.
[This place we’re at is called "The Avenue of Sphinxes"]
This is a place known as the Avenue of Sphinxes.
So they were all sphinxes.
[Staff] You all saw
the countless number of sphinxes here, right?
Yes.
[The Avenue of Sphinxes]
This is the Luxor Temple,
[From Luxor Temple to Karnak Temple in the north]
And there’s a place called Karnak Temple.
[there are countless sphinxes]
These sphinxes
[lined up for about 2.7 km]
supposedly connect all the way there.
[At the Opet Festival,
during the annual Nile flood season,]
[It was used as the Pharaoh’s parade route]
This is the path that was used for festival processions.
[The immortal Sphinx
shines brilliantly in the dark]
[WANGGEOZ, Assalamu Alaykum]
[Staff] When you think of
the Sphinx, what comes to mind?
A quiz.
That's right.
Starting right now in this place,
[The "Sphinx's Riddle" mission]
The Sphinx's Riddle!
Oh!
- Okay, the moment has arrived.
- We'll begin the mission.
[Staff] Use all
the knowledge you’ve got…
(Clap)
Whoo!
And solve the riddle
placed in front of each Sphinx.
Each?
Each?!
As you move one space at a time,
the team that conquers
[The first team to pass through wins]
the Avenue of the Sphinx first wins!
[A team battle this time?]
Is it a team battle?
Oh, it's a team battle.
How many in a team?
[A 3 versus 3 team battle]
It’s 3 versus 3.
- Oh!
- Oh, again.
[Double Pauper JISUNG is desperate to win]
Please, JISUNG! Please!
[Double Prince DAWN
is just oozing with ease]
[Freely splitting into teams of 3]
You can decide the teams this time.
[Tension]
Phew!
What vibe are we going for?
Or how about
something like this?
[Traditional vibes]
Old and young, something like that?
[Old Boy VS Young Boy]
Old and Young.
I’ve never tried
Old and Young before.
What about "YB"?
[Eager agreement]
It's good.
[OB team: LEETEUK, SHINDONG]
How should we split Team YB?
[And who else?]
Who’s with us two?
- Me!
Oh, wait, scratch that!
Me!
[Second thoughts]
Ah, no, don’t do this!
Why? Why? Why?
Why? Why?
(Quickly, to our team)
[LEETEUK joins Team Old faster than anyone else]
- Oh, it's like this?
- It's like this.
It's like, this, it's like this.
Because…
[DAWN with good vibes rises in popularity]
DAWN's got a good vibe going on.
That's why
DAWN's been prince-prince.
JISUNG’s vibe is totally off.
No, no, no.
Is the team okay?
[Will be based on Double Pauper JISUNG's agreement]
Let's at least give JISUNG the choice.
JISUNG, what do you think?
Let’s go! Let’s do this!
It's a go for me!
Oh!
[Experienced Team OB VS Powerfully passionate Team YB]
Go, go!
Okay, let's do this!
[Teams OB vs YB chosen unanimously]
Today's 3 versus 3 team lineup is
Team OB.
(Lights, Bam!)
OB!
[Jealous JOHNNY]
The timing of the lighting was crazy!
[I like OB]
Team OB! Bam!
[OLD VS YOUNG]
And here's Team YB.
[LEETEUK, SHINDONG, DAWN VS JOHNNY, KIM YOHAN, JISUNG]
Yeah!
[There will be 3 rounds for this game]
The quiz is spread over 3 rounds.
[Each round has a different quiz category]
Every round features a different category.
Oh…
Round 1 is…
[The Round 1 quiz is…]
Everyone, on your left…
[Happening at the left Sphinx]
Ah, over on the left.
[15 Sphinxes are quiz-ready]
The 15 Sphinxes lined up on the left
(I'm ready)
have questions prepared.
Team OB and Team YB,
[Start from the Sphinxes at opposite ends]
Start at the opposite ends,
tackle the same questions,
[and conquer the Sphinx in the middle]
It goes like this! Like this!
We get closer to each other.
Okay, okay.
[A face that's trying to understand]
Oh…
[The Sphinx’s Riddle]
[Team OB / Team YB]
[A quiz race unfolding
at Luxor Temple]
[The members of the first team to win
two out of three rounds become princes]
[You must solve the riddles in
front of each Sphinx to move forward]
[The team that cracks the riddle
at the 8th Sphinx in the center first wins]
[The team]
The team that arrives first
[that solves the riddle at the 8th Sphinx]
and solves the 8th riddle
[in the center first wins Round 1!]
will win Round 1.
[Staff] Let me explain
how this quiz will take place.
Each player gets
one chance to answer per question.
[Each team gets 3 chances per quiz!]
Even if you mess up, you can try three times.
What if all
three members get it wrong?
[Staff] There’s a Korean saying for this.
Oh my god.
If your head is empty…
- Your body suffers.
I guess we have to do something.
[Put arms over each other's shoulders]
The three of you will put your arms over each other's shoulders
[and do 5 group squats]
and do 5 squats together.
- Oh, okay, okay.
- That's fine, that's fine.
[Three chances to answer per quiz!]
I thought we'd have to run all the way to the temple and back.
[The three members of each team]
and run back.
[can shout an answer once]
Our thighs are gonna get rock solid.
[If all three members
answer incorrectly,]
[after doing 5 group squats,
they can move on to the next Sphinx]
[Get it together]
[A chant is required]
When you go down, "Get it"!
When you go up, "Together"!
Get it together!
Oh, wait.
[Even if you mess up and do your squat,]
You can move on even if you mess up?
[you can move on to the next Sphinx]
After the squats?
(Except for the 8th question)
Yes.
[Sharp and fiery]
It's actually better for me to use my body.
[Staff] It’s pretty dark in here right now.
For us to check
(Spotted)
where you are very quickly,
[After crossing mountains and seas,]
we'll be giving you some special items.
[the special items]
Wow, they look like stage costumes.
[Cutting-edge team vests that
you could rock on any music show stage in]
- Red?
- Yeah, red.
[OB: Red vest]
We're green for go!
[YB: Green vest]
They're NCT, so give them that color.
[Definitely stands out]
Yeah.
Just for today, I'm part of NCT.
I feel like we need to
go control traffic somewhere.
[Our JISUNG wears
that vest in a funny way]
JISUNG, there's a zipper.
There is?
Oh, you're right!
Is JISUNG already struggling?
(Dizzy)
Did JISUNG just try
to wear it over his head?
JISUNG, this is a game
where you use your head.
[Warming up his brain]
Okay, whoa, whoa! Okay!
I felt like
I needed to have
an image makeover here.
I’m gonna carry this game
and become the prince!
And I want to make DAWN
(The dark turn of Pauper JISUNG)
experience the pauper life.
The fact that we're older
means that we've survived,
so I was feeling confident.
[YOHAN] I wonder
what the questions will be like.
[JISUNG] I’m so curious.
I hope it’s not some
nonsense riddle, but a real quiz.
[YOHAN] You studied a lot, right?
[JOHNNY] I think
JISUNG is feeling good today.
I really…!
I really studied a lot!
[SHINDONG] But I feel like
we’re gonna dominate this.
I know, right?
JISUNG was seriously
glued to his phone all day,
[Got a hunch]
watching quizzes about Egypt.
- Oh, really? He watched a lot of quizzes?
- Yes, yes.
Please leak some questions, please.
Or, let's quickly
search up some answers now.
[JOHNNY] JISUNG, our ace of today!
[JISUNG] Okay!!!
I wanna keep this fun and light,
but today, I’m definitely sleeping
at the princes’ accommodation!
[JOHNNY] This is the real deal!
- Once you've slept at the prince's accommodation…
- Yes.
- the treatment is totally different!
- I feel like it'd be totally different.
[JOHNNY] After we wrap today,
let’s grab a beer and call it a night.
We have to, we have to.
[JISUNG] I'm craving
pasta…and pizza.
[The third status mission begins]
[Team YB]
[Team OB]
[They move to opposite ends
of the row of sphinxes]
[OB / YB]
[Ready to roll]
[Sphinx’s Riddle, Round 1]
Alright, first question!
[Category: Egypt]
Go ahead!
Read it, read it, read it.
Say the English spelling of Egypt.
The English spelling of Egypt.
[DAWN takes a shot]
E-G-Y-P-T.
[Fail]
??Why??
Egypt?
[The spelling for Egypt]
It’s E-G-Y-P-T, though?
[Brain freeze]
[Staff] Everyone,
you have to read the question carefully.
(Bringing their heads together)
[Unfolding at the massive temple]
Okay, we're fast. We're fast right now.
We gotta go quickly!
We gotta go! We gotta go!
[The third status showdown]
This is no good.
[Serious mode ON]
I'm gonna be serious about this today.
Forget making it fun.
[Running till their feet sweat]
Let’s go, let’s go!
Hurry up!
Hurry, hurry!
[Solve the Sphinx’s riddle]
Hurry, hurry, and tell us!
[Will it be the seasoned Team OB?]
That’s right!
[Or the daring Team YB?]
Whoa! Be careful! JISUNG, be careful!
No, what was that?
What was it? What was it?
I’m losing it.
[Who will win this
totally unpredictable battle?]
[And the third destination appears]
It really feels like we're at a vacation spot.
[At last, a chill vacation spot]
Traveling is all about
chilling and resting.
[Full of excitement, WANGGEOZ is on the move]
I think it'll be amazing.
My heart was fluttering.
[A paradise hugged by the Red Sea]
Wow!
[Egypt’s hidden gem]
This is so beautiful.
This is so nice!
[HURGHADA]
That beautiful view!
[Arrived after splitting through the Red Sea]
Wow, this is just…!
It's like something
that you'd see in a movie!
This is so nice!
[The entire island is]
Are we seriously the only ones here?
[WANGGEOZ's stage]
Wow, this is amazing.
This is crazy!
[An exclusive WANGGEOZ resort]
There's a pool over there! Amazing!
[And a surprise gift too?!]
Wow!
[Don’t miss next week!]
Wow, this is the best!
- The best!
- This was the best!